<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hardware on Hugo Quick Start Site</title>
    <link>https://example.org/tags/hardware/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Hardware on Hugo Quick Start Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2013 15:06:00 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://example.org/tags/hardware/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>DFRobot Wireless Joystick 1.1 (DFR0182)</title>
      <link>https://example.org/2013/08/dfrobot-wireless-joystick-11-dfr0182_13.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2013 15:06:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/2013/08/dfrobot-wireless-joystick-11-dfr0182_13.html</guid>
      <description>Wireless Joystick Sketch&#xA;Wireless Joystick Schematic&#xA;DFRobot Wiki Page&#xA;The DFRobot&amp;rsquo;s Wireless Joystick V1.1 is similar in size and shape to an XBox controller. The controller, or gamepad as it is also referred to, is an Arduino Deumilanove w/ATMega 328 and requires either an FTDI Basic Breakout or USB Serial Light Adapter to program. The board uses 3.3V, when connecting either the FTDI or USB Adapter verify correct voltage is set on the adapter, via jumpers on the adapter, otherwise you will burn out the gamepad.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coding Horror: Because Everyone Needs a Router</title>
      <link>https://example.org/2010/09/coding-horror-because-everyone-needs.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2010 07:05:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/2010/09/coding-horror-because-everyone-needs.html</guid>
      <description>Coding Horror: Because Everyone Needs a Router: &amp;ldquo;Buffalo Nfiniti Wireless-N High Power Router ($80)&amp;rdquo;&#xA;Jeff Atwood discusses routers and what he did to build a new one. He used the Buffalo Nfiniti Wireless-N and DD-WRT to replace his aging yet functional DGL-4500.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Debian</title>
      <link>https://example.org/2005/10/debian.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2005 13:45:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/2005/10/debian.html</guid>
      <description>I’ve tried several Linux distributions: Redhat, Coral, Suse, Mandrake, Damn Small Linux, Knoppix, Gentoo and finally Debian. Of all of these I was most loyal to Gentoo because it was the distro I learned the most with. The problem with Gentoo though is you spend so much time getting it to run and tweaking it that you don’t really get to use the machine for what you want to.&#xA;For example, I tried and successfully setup a Gentoo desktop on a couple of occasions.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
