<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>utility on Hugo Quick Start Site</title>
    <link>https://example.org/tags/utility/</link>
    <description>Recent content in utility on Hugo Quick Start Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2010 20:25:00 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://example.org/tags/utility/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>UOW: FileHelpers</title>
      <link>https://example.org/2010/10/uow-filehelpers.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2010 20:25:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/2010/10/uow-filehelpers.html</guid>
      <description>The utility of the week is FileHelpers, a .Net library that works with delimited and fixed length files. It helps to import and export data from files, strings or streams.&#xA;I found this recently as I needed to process several CSV files but I did not want to write by hand a parser. Been there, done that way too many times so I did a search and what do you know- someone smarter than me already did it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Resharper vs CodeRush</title>
      <link>https://example.org/2006/06/resharper-vs-coderush.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2006 20:48:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/2006/06/resharper-vs-coderush.html</guid>
      <description>So I used Resharper for a long time and I really liked it. There were a few things I didn’t like, especially the time added to a project load. And every once in a while it would lock up. But the features I liked were very useful: Find all usages, simple keyboard shortcuts, code reformatting. But the two most useful things it did was 1) to but a bar along the right side of the screen with orange or red lines for were the code had problems, and 2) clean up the using statements.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SqlAssist, SQL Intellisense</title>
      <link>https://example.org/2006/04/sqlassist-sql-intellisense.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2006 20:41:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/2006/04/sqlassist-sql-intellisense.html</guid>
      <description>SqlAssist, SQL Intellisense.&#xA;SqlAssist offers advanced SQL intellisense and script debugging inside the Microsoft Visual Studio .NET IDE.&#xA;Edit, test, and run scripts just like you do in SQL Server Management Studio. Use SQL pretty formatting, user configurable code templates, and many shortcuts all designed to enhance your SQL coding experience and reduce development time.&#xA;This has got to be one of the coolest add-ins to Visual Studio I have found in a long time!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NOAA Satellite Link</title>
      <link>https://example.org/2005/09/noaa-satellite-link.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2005 21:59:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/2005/09/noaa-satellite-link.html</guid>
      <description>NOAA Satellite and Information Service Good place to find imagery of Hurricanes.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
